<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://kb.cmpny.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://kb.cmpny.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-05-03T18:02:47-07:00</updated><id>https://kb.cmpny.com/</id><title type="html">CMPNY KB</title><subtitle>IT Knowledge Base by Tech Futures.</subtitle><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><entry><title type="html">Bring Your Own Printer (BYOP)</title><link href="https://kb.cmpny.com/getting-started/bring-your-own-printer-byop/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bring Your Own Printer (BYOP)" /><published>2018-05-03T16:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-05-03T16:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://kb.cmpny.com/getting-started/bring-your-own-printer-byop</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://kb.cmpny.com/getting-started/bring-your-own-printer-byop/">&lt;p&gt;If you would like to connect your own printer to the network please follow the steps below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-connect-your-printer-to-the-network&quot;&gt;1. Connect your printer to the network&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connect your printer to a wired network jack or wireless via WiFi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Network Jack - simply plug it in via a physical ethernet cable to a free network jack in your office&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;WiFi - Connect your printer to the &lt;em&gt;Spacekraft Shared&lt;/em&gt; wireless network. Ask the Space Manager for the network password.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-email-our-it-team-to-complete-setup&quot;&gt;2. Email our IT team to complete setup&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have successfully connected your printer to the network, please email &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:support@cmpny.com?subject=BYOP%20Request&amp;amp;body=Name%3A%0ACMPNY%20Location%3A%0AOffice%20%23%3A%0APrinter%20MAC%20address%3A&quot;&gt;support@cmpny.com&lt;/a&gt; with the below information:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Name&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CMPNY Location&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Office #&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Printer MAC address (see below to find it)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-find-printer-mac-address&quot;&gt;How to find printer MAC address&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will be in one of the following formats:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-bash highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;e0:55:3d:8c:c3:f3
e0-55-3d-8c-c3-f3
e0553d8cc3f3
E0:55:3D:8C:C3:F3
E0-55-3D-8C-C3-F3
E0553D8CC3F3
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Look at the product manual cover. Some manufacturers attach a MAC address label to the printer manual. This is usually noted with the legend: “Physical Address” or “MAC Address.” If this label is absent, proceed to the next step.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Consult the manual for instructions on printing the device’s configuration page.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt; Find a sticker on the printer that says “Physical Address” or “MAC Address”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-next-steps&quot;&gt;3. Next steps&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Building a Jekyll site with the default theme is just the first step. The real magic happens when you start creating blog posts, using the front matter to control templates and layouts, and taking advantage of all the awesome configuration options Jekyll makes available.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><summary type="html">If you would like to connect your own printer to the network please follow the steps below:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Which Wireless Networks to Use and How to Connect</title><link href="https://kb.cmpny.com/network/which-wireless-networks-to-use-and-how-to-connect/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Which Wireless Networks to Use and How to Connect" /><published>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://kb.cmpny.com/network/which-wireless-networks-to-use-and-how-to-connect</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://kb.cmpny.com/network/which-wireless-networks-to-use-and-how-to-connect/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are 4 wireless networks available for use at Spackeraft. This guide will outline which network to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;spacekraft&quot;&gt;Spacekraft&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Description: This is the primary network available for all Spacekraft members. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Function: It isolates all devices connected to it, meaning one devices cannot see or talk to another device on the network. To access the internet and Spackeraft Printer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use: To connect, look for Spacekraft network. For the password please see the front desk or login to this portal then see the Wireless Networks Passwords page. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;spacekraft-shared&quot;&gt;Spacekraft Shared&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Description: For private office members to share devices within their own office only. Or for any member wishing to share or view devices with each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Function: To share legacy devices such as personal printers or any devices that does not support WPA2-Enterprise authentication. For private office members, if it is a printer or example no one else will be able to view it except those in your office or organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use: For private office members, connect your devices to Spacekraft Shared network. For the password please see the front desk or login to this portal then see the Wireless Networks Passwords page.  On the support portal, click request new service, select Networking Provisioning &amp;gt; Add legacy device, and fill out the required information. For other members wishing to share files for example simply connect both devices to the Spaekraft Shared network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;spacekraft-private&quot;&gt;Spacekraft Private&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Description: For private office members , it creates a virtual network which bridges the wired network and wireless so they can share files and view devices within their organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Function: Allows you to view any device connected via wired or wireless and share files and talk to each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use: This network is hidden, to connect please see the Windows, Mac OS X or Android guide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;cloudsingularity-open&quot;&gt;CloudSingularity Open&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Description: For guests and events to access the internet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Function: It is a throttled network with bandwidth restrictions to allow guests to easily connect to the internet without any username or password.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use: There is no authentication required, however you will need to accept the terms of service. When you connect open a web browser and navigate to any webpage, and you will be promoted with a splash page.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unable to Contact Server - Error</title><link href="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/unable-to-contact-server-error/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unable to Contact Server - Error" /><published>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/unable-to-contact-server---error</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/unable-to-contact-server-error/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When attempting to use a fob to login to the printer a popup screen with the message “Unable to Contact Server” may appear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it does, please wait 5-10 seconds and try again. This is caused when the printer is in sleep mode for an extended period of time.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Section B: IT Policy</title><link href="https://kb.cmpny.com/network/section-b-it-policy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Section B: IT Policy" /><published>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://kb.cmpny.com/network/section-b-it-policy</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://kb.cmpny.com/network/section-b-it-policy/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;Below is a copy of the CMPNY IT Policy, as per the member agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Spacekraft agrees to provide Internet access via WiFi or wired connection on an “as is” basis to the Licensee as part of the Licensed Space. Only a single device may be connected to a wired network port at any one-time. Exceptions may be made for SIP phones with built in PC ports. See section 13.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Spacekraft agrees to provide pay per use printer access to the Licensee.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Spacekraft agrees  to provide support on a best effort basis during the hours of 9AM-5PM via on-site support or the support portal (support.spacekraft.co), for the following issues only:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a. Getting connected to the Spacekraft Network (the “Network”) and the Internet via wireless or wired connection on the following operating systems:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 7, 8, 8.1 and 10&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Apple OS X 10.6, 10.7, 10.8, 10.9, 10.10, 10.11&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Apple iOS (stock, un-modified or rooted)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Google Android (stock, un-modified or rooted)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;b. Being able to print to the Spacekraft printer from supported operating systems:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 7, 8, 8.1 and 10&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Apple OS X 10.6, 10.7, 10.8, 10.9, 10.10, 10.11&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Licensee will not use the Network or internet connection provided by Spacekraft to conduct illegal activities (illegal activities are those which are considered criminal acts in British Columbia or Canada - examples: wire fraud, distributing child pornography, hatemail, etc.).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Licensee will not disrupt the normal functioning of the Spacekraft network by altering it via software (e.g. DDOS attacks or any other activity that would result in loss of service) or hardware (cutting cables, damaging routers, etc.).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Licensee’s outgoing communications (which are tied to Spacekraft’s IP addresses) will comply with Canada’s Anti-Spam Legislation so that our IP addresses are not blacklisted from incoming mail servers worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Licensee will not access other Spacekraft Licensees’ computer systems or software as a service (SAAS - e.g. webmail) without their explicit authorization.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Licensee will not engage in activities that could violate our service agreement with our ISP (Tech Futures Interactive Inc.). Examples: disseminating materials that violate copyright or intellectual property rights (read - torrents). More information on Tech Futures Acceptable Use Policy can be found on their website, www.techfutures.xyz&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Licensee will not make unauthorized attempts to collect and/or disclose personal information of your fellow Spacekraft users.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Licensee will not make unauthorized attempts to circumvent computer security methods, operating systems or probing for exposures in other systems or networks.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;To ensure fair network access for all users, Spacekraft at its sole discretion may mange the network using the following methods:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rate limiting the speed and/or bandwidth available for wireless or wired connections&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Filtering or restricting certain content or protocols&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The Licensee agrees that Spacekraft may without notice, and at its sole discretion monitor and review all network traffic.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;To ensure the performance and security of the network, no devices that create their own wireless signal or devices that increase the number of wired ports may be used on Spacekraft’s network. Such devices could be but is not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Portable Wi-Fi hotspots&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wireless routers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Printers with direct wireless printing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Switches&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Routers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If such a device is required, it must be pre-approved by Spacekraft before its use on the network. Any device not pre-approved will be automatically blocked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Licensee is not permitted to operate any servers that would serve content outside the Spacekraft network such as but not limited to email, web or voice servers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><summary type="html">Below is a copy of the CMPNY IT Policy, as per the member agreement.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Scan to Email</title><link href="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/scan-to-email/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Scan to Email" /><published>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/scan-to-email</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/scan-to-email/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Login with your fob or username/password&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Scroll down to the bottom of the menu and select E-mail &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fill in the email address you want to send to in the “To” field. All other fields are optional.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Printer Setup - Windows</title><link href="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/printer-setup-windows/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Printer Setup - Windows" /><published>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/printer-setup---windows</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/printer-setup-windows/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;Install the drivers and client app or use email-to-print to quickly get started. Spacekraft Print Services powered by Tech Futures provides full colour, black and white full duplex printing, automatic stapling, scanning, fax and copying capabilities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that that the links below will only work if you are connected to “Spacekraft” wifi network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 1: Create a new password&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Head over to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://accounts.cmpny.com/pwm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Accounts Management Portal&lt;/a&gt; and create a new password for your account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your username is in the format of first name (dot) last name, for example Captain.Kirk. Your password is the same network password for the rest of Spacekraft’s IT Services,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For further information please visit the &lt;a href=&quot;/getting-started/create-a-new-password/&quot;&gt;Create a New Password&lt;/a&gt; guide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 2: Download drivers and client app&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Download the client application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have downloaded the client app zip folder, extract it first then launch the file labeled client-local-install.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may be prompted to login using the same username and password as in step 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have successfully logged in, you should see the account balance window.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 3: Open Printers and Scanners&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open Contorl Panel, then open Devices &amp;amp; Printers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once open, click Add Printer on the top toolbar. The following window will appear, choose The Printer that I want isn’t listed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 4: Add Printer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Select the shared printer by name option, and copy the image by entering \\10.210.10.3\HP MFP&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Installation may take 1-5 minutes, and the following screen will appear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A popup window may appear asking for a name and password. Enter “SPACEKRAFT\” followed by the same username and password as in step 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the printer has been successfully added you will see the following screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 4.1: Configure Printer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right click the printer and select Printer properties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Select the Device Settings tab and set Tray 3 as HP 1500-Sheet Input Tray and Tray 4 as HP 2000-Sheet Input Tray.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Setup Complete&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time printing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first time you print a document a popup window will appear requiring your username and password. Enter your same username and password as in step 1. You may choose for your computer to remember your username/password until you logout so it will not prompt you every time you print.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Success!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have successfully printed a document, a message will appear saying your document has been held in a queue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proceed to the printer to release your document. See the guide on using print release for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><summary type="html">Install the drivers and client app or use email-to-print to quickly get started. Spacekraft Print Services powered by Tech Futures provides full colour, black and white full duplex printing, automatic stapling, scanning, fax and copying capabilities. </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Printer Setup - Mac OS X</title><link href="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/printer-setup-mac-os-x/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Printer Setup - Mac OS X" /><published>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/printer-setup---mac-os-x</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/printer-setup-mac-os-x/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This Article applies to Burnaby Only&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Install the drivers and client app or use email-to-print to quickly get started. Spacekraft Print Services powered by Tech Futures provides full colour, black and white full duplex printing, automatic stapling, scanning, fax and copying capabilities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please note that that the links below will only work if you are connected to &amp;ldquo;Spacekraft&amp;rdquo; wifi network.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;step-1-create-a-new-password&quot;&gt;Step 1: Create a new password&lt;a href=&quot;#step-1-create-a-new-password&quot; class=&quot;header-link&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Head over to the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://accounts.cmpny.com/pwm&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Accounts Management Portal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and create a new password for your account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your username is in the format of first name (dot) last name, for example Captain.Kirk.  &lt;br /&gt;Your password is the same network password for the rest of Spacekraft’s IT Services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For further information please visit the &lt;a href=&quot;/getting-started/create-a-new-password/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create a New Password&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; guide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;step-2-download-drivers-and-client-app&quot;&gt;Step 2: Download drivers and client app&lt;a href=&quot;#step-2-download-drivers-and-client-app&quot; class=&quot;header-link&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Download the &lt;a href=&quot;http://spacekraft.goprint.xyz/client/mac.zip&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Client Application&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://spacekraft.goprint.xyz/drivers/mac_drivers.zip&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drivers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have downloaded the client app, (right/control-clicking and selecting “Open”) open the file labeled client-local-install. After that is complete, install the drivers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;blob:https://app.cloudcannon.com/40d8fb51-1812-40a8-8f68-722f25a36ba3&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;step-3-open-printers-and-scanners&quot;&gt;Step 3: Open Printers and Scanners&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open System Preferences, then open Printers &amp;amp; Scanners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once open, right click (control+click) the top toolbar and select Customize Toolbar. Drag and drop the Advanced icon into the toolbar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;step-4-add-printer&quot;&gt;Step 4: Add Printer&lt;a href=&quot;#step-4-add-printer&quot; class=&quot;header-link&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under the Advanced tab, copy the image below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter the same information as shown in Type, Device and URL. You may use any Name and Location you want. For the Use field select Select Software… and choose the driver named HP LaserJet 700 Color MFP M775.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;step-41-configure-printer&quot;&gt;Step 4.1: Configure Printer&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set Tray 3 as HP 1500-Sheet Input Tray and Tray 4 as HP 2000-Sheet Input Tray. On the bottom, check the box next to HP 500-Sheet Stapler/Stacker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;step-42-printer-authentication&quot;&gt;Step 4.2: Printer Authentication&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A popup window may appear asking for a name and password. Enter “SPACEKRAFT\” followed by the same username and password as in step 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;step-5-setup-complete&quot;&gt;Step 5: Setup Complete&lt;a href=&quot;#step-5-setup-complete&quot; class=&quot;header-link&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you have completed the above steps, you should see a screen similar the the one below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First time printing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first time you print a document a popup window will appear requiring your username and password. Enter your same username and password as in step 1. You may choose for your computer to remember your username/password until you logout so it will not prompt you every time you print.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Success!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have successfully printed a document, the following message will appear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proceed to the printer to release your document. See the guide on using print release for more information.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><summary type="html">This Article applies to Burnaby Only</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Print Release</title><link href="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/print-release/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Print Release" /><published>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/print-release</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/print-release/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;releasing-documents-held-in-queue&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;Releasing documents held in queue&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt; print jobs sent to the queue will only be held for a couple hours before they are automatically removed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Login with your fob or username/password. Once successfully logged in the following message will appear with your username.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Select the Print Release icon&lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All your printer jobs will be displayed, if you have multiple documents in the queue they will all be selected by default. Use the check boxes to select the documents you want to print. Details on the print jobs will be displayed on the right once you click the “I” icon. Once you are ready to print, select the Print button on the bottom right of the screen.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><summary type="html">Releasing documents held in queue</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Price Guide</title><link href="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/price-guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Price Guide" /><published>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/price-guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/price-guide/">&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;printing-and-copying&quot;&gt;Printing and Copying&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;If it does, please wait 5-10 seconds and try again. This is caused when the printer is in sleep mode for an extended period of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;printing-and-copying-1&quot;&gt;Printing and Copying&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;content&quot;&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th class=&quot;current&quot;&gt;Size&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Color&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Grayscale&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Color duplex&lt;div&gt;(each side)&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Grayscale duplex&lt;p style=&quot;margin-bottom:15px;&quot; class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;(each side)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr data-paper-size=&quot;A0&quot;&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p style=&quot;margin-bottom:15px;&quot; class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;LETTER &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-family: Roboto, 'Helvetica Neue', Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; font-weight: normal;&quot;&gt;(ANSI_A)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.50&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.10&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.48&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.08&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr data-paper-size=&quot;LETTER&quot;&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p style=&quot;margin-bottom:15px;&quot; class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;LEGAL &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-family: Roboto, 'Helvetica Neue', Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; font-weight: normal;&quot;&gt;(LEGAL-14)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.55&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.15&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.53&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.13&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr data-paper-size=&quot;LEGAL&quot;&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p style=&quot;margin-bottom:15px;&quot; class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-family: Roboto, 'Helvetica Neue', Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; font-weight: normal;&quot;&gt;11X17 &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-family: Roboto, 'Helvetica Neue', Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif; font-size: 13px; font-weight: normal;&quot;&gt;(Ledger)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$1.00&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.50&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.98&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.48&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr data-paper-size=&quot;FOLIO&quot;&gt;&lt;td&gt;Other&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.50&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.10&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;$0.50&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;$0.10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;scan-to-email&quot;&gt;Scan to Email&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Free&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;faxing&quot;&gt;Faxing&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sending: $0.05/page&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Receiving: PDF, $0.05/page. Printed, $0.13/page (automatic duplex).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;present-before-paste&quot;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Known issue - Unable to print when connected to Spacekraft Private network (Burnaby)</title><link href="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/known-issue-unable-to-print-when-connected-to-spacekraft-private-network-burnaby/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Known issue - Unable to print when connected to Spacekraft Private network (Burnaby)" /><published>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-03-05T16:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/known-issue---unable-to-print-when-connected-to-spacekraft-private-network-burnaby</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://kb.cmpny.com/print%20services%20(burnaby)/known-issue-unable-to-print-when-connected-to-spacekraft-private-network-burnaby/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Known issues:&lt;br /&gt;At this time you cannot print  to the Spacekraft printer while connected to Spacekraft Private network. Please disconnect and connect to the regular Spacekraft network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This applies to Burnaby only.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;name&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;email&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;nil}</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>